来吧!
Come on!
你能做到的!进入二垒!
You can do it! Get in to second!
加油，伙计们，你们要把比赛拱手让人了!
Come on, guys! You're giving this game away!
来吧!把它捡起来!
Come on! Pick it up!
来吧,芬尼。来吧。
Come on, Finney. Come on.
加油，你可以的。
Let's go. You got this.
开球!-你能行的，芬尼。
-Play ball! -You got this, Finney.
一振!
Strike!
是的,芬尼!不错,芬尼!
Yes, Finney! Nice, Finney!
我们走吧,芬尼。再来两次
Let's go, Finney. Two more strikes.
挥棒  击球
Swing, batter, batter. Swing, batter, batter.
二振!
Strike two!
是啊!
Yeah!
睁大眼睛。眼睛睁开。
Eyes open out there. Eyes open.
哦,不。哦,不。
Oh, no. Oh, no.
全垒打!
Home run!
布鲁斯!布鲁斯!布鲁斯!
Bruce! Bruce! Bruce!
布鲁斯!布鲁斯!
Bruce! Bruce!
布鲁斯!布鲁斯!布鲁斯!布鲁斯!
Bruce! Bruce! Bruce! Bruce!
布鲁斯!布鲁斯!
Bruce! Bruce!
布鲁斯!布鲁斯!布鲁斯!布鲁斯!
Bruce! Bruce! Bruce! Bruce!
布鲁斯!布鲁斯!布鲁斯!布鲁斯!布鲁斯!布鲁斯!布鲁斯!布鲁斯!
Bruce! Bruce! Bruce! Bruce! Bruce! Bruce! Bruce! Bruce!
嘿,伙计。
Hey, dude.
伙计，你的胳膊真漂亮。
Man, your arm is mint.
你差点就骗到我了。
You almost had me.
打得好-打得好。
-Good game. -Good game.
♪山是高的，山谷是低的
♪ The mountain is high, the valley is low ♪
嗨,布鲁斯。
Hi, Bruce.
♬你不知道该走哪条路
♪ And you're confused on which way to go ♪
所以我来这里是要帮你们的
♪ So I've come here to give you a hand ♪
并把你引入♬
♪ And lead you into ♪
♪希望之地，所以♪哦…♪
-♪ The promised land, so ♪ -♪ Ooh... ♪
♬来吧，搭便车吧♬
♪ Come on and take a free ride ♪
♬搭便车♬
♪ Free ride ♪
♬来吧，坐在我身边♬
♪ Come on and sit here by my side ♪
♬来吧，搭便车吧♬
♪ Come on and take a free ride ♪
你能不能声音再大点?
You think you can slurp that a little louder?
我觉得在博尔德他们听不到你说话。
I don't think they can hear you up in Boulder.
对不起,爸爸。
Sorry, Daddy.
我不知道。
I don't know.
大家都说方兹或里奇。
Everyone says Fonzie or Richie.
米莉说的是波西，但我认为任何人都不应该相信一个想长大后和波西结婚的人。
Millie says Potsie, but I don't think anyone should ever trust anyone who wants to grow up and marry Potsie.
我想我还是坚持我现在的计划嫁给丹尼·伯纳杜斯吧。
I think I'll just stick with my current plan and marry Danny Bonaduce.
你不能嫁给帕特里奇家族的人。
You're not gonna marry a member of the Partridge Family.
他是如此重要。
He's so crucial.
我喜欢他的声音。
I love his voice.
这是新的。
It's new.
什么?
What?
传单。
The flyer.
山田先生又把它们挂起来了。
Mr. Yamada is putting them up again.
你觉得他们不会找到他们的，对吧?
You don't think they're gonna find them, do you?
这不是他们想要的。
Not how they want to.
来吧。我们走吧。
Come on. Let's go.
我们要迟到了。
We're gonna be late.
-来吧!-嘿,过来!
-Come on! -Hey, come here!
战斗!战斗!战斗!战斗!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
战斗!战斗!战斗!战斗!战斗!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
战斗!战斗!
Fight! Fight!
你以为你很厉害吗?
You think you're so tough, huh?
让我们找出答案。
Let's find out.
我要像敲钉子一样敲你，你这个骨瘦如柴的小胖子。
I will pound you like a nail, you scrawny little beaner.
然后去做。
Then do it.
除非你是害怕。
Unless you're scared.
让他,罗宾!
Get him, Robin!
起来!
Get up!
打他更难!
Hit him harder!
来吧。
Come on.
天呐
Holy shit.
我们走吧。我们走吧。
Let's go. Let's go.
这到底是怎么回事?
What the hell?
——是驼鹿。我不在乎。
-That was Moose. -I don't care.
驼鹿是个大混蛋。
Moose is a giant asshole.
我知道。
I know.
但是去年，当他把你的鼻子弄出血的时候…格温。-他自找的。
But last year, when he made your nose bleed... -Gwen. -He had it coming.
没有人会这样。
No one has that coming.
-芬尼，他揍了你。我知道,格温。
-Finney, he beat you up. -I know, Gwen.
我当时在场，记得吗?
I was there, remember?
我…我只是不想谈这件事。
I... I just don't want to talk about it.
他跟罗宾·阿雷利亚诺吵架真是太蠢了。
Well, he was stupid to pick a fight with Robin Arellano.
他是学校里最强悍的孩子了自从抢球侠把弹球侠万斯·霍珀挖走。
He's the toughest kid in school since The Grabber got Pinball Vance Hopper.
我希望你别这么叫他。
I wish you wouldn't call him that.
大家都叫他弹球万斯。
Everyone called him Pinball Vance.
不,我的意思是……我知道你说的是谁，混蛋脸。
No, I mean... I know who you mean, jerk face.
连报纸都称他为抓人贼。
Even the papers call him The Grabber.
只是…我希望你不要说出他的名字。
Just... I wish you wouldn't say his name.
你不会真的相信那个故事吧?
You don't actually believe that story, do you?
-不。-因为他听不到。
-No. -Because he can't hear you.
他不太接受孩子们这么说。
He doesn't really take kids that say it.
-我知道。芬尼。
-I know that. -Finney.
-我说我知道。那么说。
-I said I know. -Then say it.
不。
No.
你是鸡吗?
Are you chicken?
我不是故意的。
I didn't mean it.
我知道。
I know.
内核是固态的。外核是熔融的。
The inner core is solid. The outer core is molten.
下一层被称为地幔，大部分是固体。
The next layer, called the mantle, is mostly solid.
然而，地幔薄的外带部分熔融。
However, the thin outer zone of the mantle is partially molten.
下一张。
Next slide.
表层被称为地壳。
The surface layer is called the crust.
它是实心的，非常薄。
It is solid and very thin.
随着地球的分层，它开始慢慢冷却，但内部仍然非常热。
As the Earth separated into layers, it began to cool slowly, but the interior was still very hot.
嘿,芬尼。
Hey, Finney.
午餐见。我给你留个座位。
See you at lunch. I'll save you a seat.
嘿,芬尼。
Hey, Finney.
出来吧，混蛋。
Come on out, dick weed.
不是在愚弄任何人，noid。
Not fooling anyone, noid.
你在我们的浴室做什么?嗯?
What you doing in our bathroom? Huh?
看到这个标志吗?它说“男孩”。
See the sign? It says "boys."
是啊，男孩，不是基佬。
Yeah, boys, not fags.
笨蛋,那就动起来吧。
Dipshits, move.
嘿,芬恩。
Hey, Finn.
发生什么事情了?
What's happening?
你知道的，我想就是继续，继续。
You know, just keeping on keeping on, I guess.
啊哈。
Uh-huh.
驼鹿的牙齿很锋利。
Moose got some damn sharp teeth.
关节第一节都流血了。
Knuckles bled all first period.
等待。
Wait.
再去他妈的芬恩…我操你。
Fuck with Finn again... I fuck with you.
你现在可以走了。
You can leave now.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
总有一天你会为自己挺身而出的。
You're gonna have to stand up for yourself one of these days.
是的,我知道。
Yeah, I know.
嘿，你为什么和慕斯打架?
Hey, why'd you fight Moose?
他只是在胡说。
He was just shit-talking.
他肯定会让步的。
Pretty sure he'd back down.
不。
Nope.
说实话，当他摇摆的时候我很惊讶。
I was so surprised when he swung, to be honest.
我的意思是，你必须这么做吗?
I mean, did you have to?
看起来你把他伤得很重。
Looked like you really hurt him.
我只是想把他打倒在地。
I was just gonna knock his ass down.
痛骂他一顿。
Whale on him a bit.
但那不会让你流血。
But that wouldn't draw no blood.
在那种情况下，流血越多越好。
In a situation like that, the more blood, the better.
为了大众，你知道吗?
For the crowd, you know?
它提出了一个更有力的观点。
It makes a stronger point.
我周五晚上看了《德州电锯杀人狂》
I've seen Texas Chain Saw Massacre Friday night.
你看到了吗?-这部电影是R级的。
-You seen it? -That movie's rated R.
我爸绝不会带我去看的。
My dad would never take me to see that.
我叔叔带我去汽车影院。
My uncle takes me to the drive-in.
我们看到一切。
We see everything.
但是，伙计，那部电影…这是有史以来最好的。
But, man, that movie... it's the best ever.
比《龙争虎斗》更好吗?
Better than Enter the Dragon?
好吧,好吧。也许第二个最好。
Well, okay. Maybe second best.
你知道的，我想有一天去看李小龙的电影。
You know, I want to see a Bruce Lee movie one day.
比如，嗯，如果它出现在电视上，你知道吗?
Like, um, maybe if it comes on TV, you know?
是的。是的,你会的。
Yeah. Yeah, you will.
你放学后有时间来我家一趟吗?
Hey, um, you got time to stop by my house after school?
又是数学吗?
Is it math again?
约翰逊先生说话太快了。
Mr. Johnson talks too fast.
他没有解释清楚。不喜欢你。
He doesn't explain it right. Not like you.
你能给我解释一下吗?
Can you walk me through it?
如果我再得个F，我就被停学了。
If I get another "F," I'm suspended.
是的,当然。
Yeah, sure.
所以，当我们用11减去6，我们发现X的值是5。
So, when we subtract six from 11, we find that the value of "X" is five.
你找我?
You wanted to see me?
格温多林·布莱克，这是莱特警探和米勒警探。
Gwendolyn Blake, this is Detective Wright and Detective Miller.
布莱克小姐。
Miss Blake.
他们想和你谈谈。
They would like to talk to you about something.
它是……你真的是艾米·山田的朋友吗?
Is it... is it true you're friends with Amy Yamada?
我们一起上班主任班。
We have homeroom together.
她是好吗?
Is she okay?
她很好。
She's fine.
你知道这是怎么回事。
You know what this is about.
关于她哥哥布鲁斯，你跟艾米说了什么?
What did you say to Amy about her brother Bruce?
只说我做了一个关于他的梦。
Just that I had a dream about him.
什么样的梦?
What kind of a dream?
只是一个奇怪的。
Just a weird one.
你梦里发生了什么?
What happened in your dream?
他拍摄。这是所有。
He was taken. That's all.
一个拿着黑色气球的人在货车里。
By a man with black balloons in a van.
是的。
Yes.
关于你的梦你还能告诉我们些什么?
What else can you tell us about your dream?
为什么?这只是一个梦。
Why? It was just a dream.
还有谁知道这个梦?
Who else knows about the dream?
没有人。
Nobody.
我们在现场发现了两个黑色气球，格温。
We found two black balloons at the scene, Gwen.
哦。
Oh.
我们还在格里芬·斯塔格被绑架的现场发现了一个黑色气球。
We also found one black balloon at the scene of Griffin Stagg's abduction.
我们从未公布过这些细节，所以…问题是，你从哪里听说气球的?
And we never released those details, so... So the question is, where did you hear about the balloons?
我没有。
I didn't.
我再问你一次。
I'm gonna ask you again.
你怎么知道气球的事?
How did you know about the balloons?
你有什么瞒着我们的，格温?
What aren't you telling us, Gwen?
要么是部门里有内奸，要么…或者什么?我是掠夺者?-不。
Either there's a leak in the department, or... -Or what? I'm The Grabber? -No.
你觉得我去年春天绑架了万斯·霍珀吗?
You think I kidnapped Vance Hopper last spring?
就是这样吗？
Is that it?
万斯被抓了两次。
Vance got held back twice.
我见过他打架，相信我，你俩谁蒙着眼睛他都能把你打得屁滚麻打。
I've seen him fight, and trust me, he could kick the shit out of either of you blindfolded.
格温，注意你的语言。
Gwen, watch your language.
是啊，我把他拿下了，因为很明显我就是抓人的，你们这些蠢屁大奶。
Yeah, I took him down 'cause obviously I'm The Grabber, you dumb fucking fart knockers.
格温多林布雷克!
Gwendolyn Blake!
格温。
Gwen.
你有什么瞒着我们的?
What aren't you telling us?
有时我的梦想是对的。
That sometimes my dreams are right.
他就在这里。
There he is.
那是什么?
What was that?
什么都没有。
Nothing.
我今晚要在苏茜家过夜。
I'm staying over at Susie's tonight.
今天是星期五，所以你知道这意味着什么。
It's Friday, so you know what that means.
我会照顾爸爸的。
I'll look after Dad.
我早上就回家了。
I'll be home in the morning.
你最好别把冰淇淋都吃了。
And you better not eat all the ice cream.
♬把那东西放低，放寂寞，孩子……♪
♪ Play that thing low and lonesome, boy... ♪
我很抱歉!
I'm sorry!
-爸爸,停止!-嘿!
-Dad, stop! -Hey!
你别插手!
You stay out of this!
Gwenny。
Gwenny.
他们来我的工作。
They came to my work.
警察为什么来我工作的地方?
Why did the police come to my work?
我不知道!我很抱歉!
I don't know! I'm sorry!
你得告诉我你对这次调查的了解。
You need to tell me what you know about this investigation.
——没有!-告诉我…什么?
-Nothing! -Tell me what... What?
没什么。嗯?
-Nothing. -Huh?
没有什么!
Nothing!
-什么? !——没有!
-What?! -Nothing!
再打我，我就把它扔了!
Hit me again, and I'm dropping it!
你敢放下枪，我就狠狠揍你一顿。
You drop that, and I will beat your ass twice as hard.
不,爸爸!
No, Dad!
那可是一瓶八块钱的伏特加!
That was an eight-dollar bottle of goddamn vodka!
现在你听我说。
Oh, now you listen to me.
听我的。你不是你妈妈!
Listen to me. You are not your mother!
我知道。
I know.
这意味着你不会听到不存在的东西。
That means you do not hear things that are not there.
你看不到不存在的东西!
You do not see things that are not there!
好吧。
Okay.
-他们不在那儿，格文妮!-好的。
-They're not there, Gwenny! -Okay.
和你的梦想……他们只是他妈的梦。
And your dreams... they're just fucking dreams.
你明白我的意思吗?-是的!
-Do you understand me? -Yes!
-你明白我的意思吗?-是的!
-Do you understand me?! -Yes!
说出来。我要听你亲口说。
Say it. I want to hear you say it.
我的梦只是梦。
My dreams are just dreams.
再说一遍!
Say it again!
我的梦只是梦!
My dreams are just dreams!
再说一遍。
Say it again.
我的梦只是梦!
My dreams are just dreams!
去看会儿电视什么的。
Go watch some television or something.
下面不要加冰，小姐。
And no ice on that bottom, young lady.
我要你想想你做了什么。
I want you to think about what you did.
你知道这件事吗?
Did you know anything about this?
你也一样。
Same goes for you.
你明白我的意思吗?
You got that?
现在,滚出去。
Now, get out.
我告诉过你，戴维。
I told you, Davey.
Sal -你受伤了吗?我没事。
-You hurt, Sal? -I'm okay.
你没事吧?
You okay?
但这是鲍勃警官说会发生的事。
Yeah, but this is what Officer Bob said would happen.
莎莉,你迟到了。
Sally, you're late.
你的自行车一团糟。
Your bike's a mess.
我也一样。
So am I.
鲍勃警官会修好那个轮子，但我现在不能问他。
Officer Bob would fix that wheel, but I can't ask him now.
为什么不呢?
Why not?
我明白了。
I understand.
谢谢您的来电。
Thank you for calling.
芬尼。
Finney.
是吗?
Yeah?
你认识一个叫罗宾的孩子吗?安巴尔…基于“增大化现实”技术的…Arellano吗?
Do you know a kid named Robin Are... A-Ar... Ar... Arellano?
是的,就是这样。
Yeah, that's it.
他是我学校的朋友。为什么?
He's a friend from school. Why?
我真的很抱歉，芬尼。
I'm really sorry, Finney.
我知道他是你的朋友。
I know he was your friend.
不要说“是”。
Don't say "was."
他是我的朋友。
He is my friend.
对不起。
Sorry.
格温。
Gwen.
你会做梦吗?
Can you do that dream thing?
事情不是那样的。
It doesn't work that way.
你有试过吗?
Have you tried?
当然有。
Of course I have.
好吧,再试一次。
Well, try again.
请。
Please.
天啊，我知道你知道我要问你什么，但我还是要问你。
Jesus, I know you know what I'm going to ask you, but I'm going to ask you anyway.
我弟弟，他需要朋友。
My brother, he needs his friend.
我知道你不能就这么放他走，因为你不会干涉什么的。
And I know you can't just let him go, because you don't interfere or whatever.
我不知道规则。
I don't know the rules.
但如果你能帮我实现一两个梦想，帮我或其他人找到他，我会永远追随你。
But if you could help me have a dream or two and just see something that could help the police or me or anyone find him, I will follow you forever.
阿们。
Amen.
别以为我不知道这里发生了什么。
Don't think I don't know what's going on in here.
熄灯后禁止玩耍。
No playing after lights-out.
对不起,爸爸。
Sorry, Daddy.
去睡觉。
Go to sleep.
我爱你。
I love you.
我也爱你，爸爸。
Love you, too, Daddy.
该死的家伙,Gwenny。
Goddamn it, Gwenny.
她又做了什么?
What the hell did she do now?
很抱歉，布莱克先生。
We're sorry, Mr. Blake.
你女儿什么都没做。
Your daughter hasn't done anything.
但我们有办法和她谈谈吗?
But is there any way we can speak with her?
他妈的cocksucking懦夫!
Fucking cocksucking cowards!
去你妈的，丑脸。
Fuck you, too, ugly ass face.
格温!
Gwen!
好吧,类。
All right, class.
这是你整个学期都在担心的一天。
It is the day you've been dreading all semester.
青蛙解剖的一天。
Frog dissection day.
选个搭档。
Uh, pick a partner.
记住，在今年剩下的时间里，你将和这位搭档搭档。
Remember, you will be paired with this partner for the rest of the year.
你需要一个搭档吗?
Do you need a partner?
哦,不,不。
Uh, no, no.
我是说，我现在还没有搭档。
I-I mean, yeah, I don't have a partner yet.
那些家伙都是混蛋。
Those guys are assholes.
-什么?——早上。
-What? -This morning.
每个人都在谈论它。
Everybody's talking about it.
哦。
Oh.
不过你妹妹真的很酷。
Your sister's really cool, though.
我希望我哥哥和我能成为那样的朋友。
I wish my brother and I were friends like that.
眼睛上面。
Eyes up here.
好吧，让我们切开一只青蛙。
All right, let's cut open a frog.
唐娜,唐娜,唐娜。
Donna, Donna, Donna.
-“哦，芬尼，你愿意做我的实验搭档吗?”停止。
-"Oh, Finney, will you be my lab partner?" -Stop.
闭嘴，你这个混蛋。
Shut up, you jerk.
好的，明天见。
All right, see you tomorrow.
你要去哪里?
Where you going?
我今晚要在苏茜家过夜。
I'm staying over at Susie's tonight.
今天是星期五,所以…我会照顾爸爸的。查查你的了,孩子。
It's Friday, so... -I'll look after Dad. -See you, kid.
哦!
Oh!
你穿帮。
You goof.
好吧，这不是桃红的渴望吗?
Well, isn't that just peachy keen?
需要帮忙吗?
You need some help?
你看到了吗?
You see that?
是的。
Yeah.
能把我的帽子递给我吗?
Would you hand me my hat?
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
我是一个兼职魔术师。
I am a part-time magician.
-你想看一个魔术吗?-是的。
-Would you like to see a magic trick? -Yeah.
是吗?
Yeah?
-那些是黑色的气球吗?-是的。
-Are those black balloons in there? -Yeah.
我他妈的的手臂。
My fucking arm.
你伤了我的胳膊，我应该扭断你的脖子。
I should snap your neck for what you did to my arm.
耶稣。
Jesus.
上面全是血。
It's covered in blood.
就像我杀了人一样。
It's like I killed someone.
你看到了吗?
You see that?
你什么都看不见。
Not like you can see shit.
我知道你很害怕。
I know you're scared.
但我不会再伤害你了。
But I'm not gonna hurt you anymore.
我说过要扭断你的脖子…
What I said about snapping your neck...
我生气了，仅此而已。
I was angry, is all.
你伤了我的胳膊。
And you did a number on my arm.
我不会跟你过不去的。嗯?
I'm not gonna hold it against you. Hmm?
我猜……现在我们扯平了。
I guess... now we're even.
你不必害怕，因为这里不会发生什么坏事。
You don't have to be scared, because nothing bad is going to happen here.
我向你保证，约翰尼。
On that I give my word, Johnny.
你喜欢苏打水吗?
You like soda?
嗯?我告诉你。
Hmm? I'll tell you what.
我去给你拿杯苏打水，然后…
I'm gonna go get you a soda, and then...
是电话吗?
Is that the phone?
你听到电话响了吗?
You hear a phone ringing?
我去看看是谁。
I'm gonna go see who it is.
那我给你拿杯苏打水。
Then I'll get you a soda.
然后我会回来解释一切。嗯?
And then I'll come back and explain everything. Hmm?
格温妮，你爸爸打电话来了。
Gwenny, your dad's on the phone.
嗨,爸爸。
Hi, Daddy.
不,我没有。自从学校。
No, I haven't. Not since school.
它不工作。
It doesn't work.
从我小时候起就没有了。
Not since I was a kid.
把它挂起来。
Hang it up.
我知道你很害怕，你想回家。
I know you're scared and you want to go home.
我很快就送你回家。
I'll take you home soon.
只是……哦，一切都搞砸了。
It's just that... Oh, everything's all fucked up.
我得去楼上待一会儿。
I got to be upstairs for a while.
事情的出现。
Something's come up.
什么?
What?
更不用说什么。
Never mind what.
有人看到什么了吗?
Did someone see something?
警察来了吗?
Are the police coming?
如果你在他们来之前放我走，我保证不会说出去。
If you let me go before they get here, I promise I won't tell.
不是警察。
It's not the police.
有人吗?
Someone, though?
有人来了吗?
Someone's coming?
我会尖叫。
I'll scream.
如果有人在楼上，他们会听到我的。
If someone's upstairs, they'll hear me.
不,他不会。门关着就不行。
No, he won't. Not with the door shut.
他吗?
He?
门关上了，没人能听到任何声音。
With the door shut, no one can hear anything down here.
我自己给它隔音的。
I soundproofed it myself.
如果你愿意，就大声喊吧。你不会打扰任何人的。
So shout if you like. You won't bother anyone.
是你杀了其他人。
You're the one who killed the others.
布鲁斯。
Bruce.
罗宾。
Robin.
那不是我。
That wasn't me.
那是另外一个人。
That was someone else.
我永远不会让你做任何你不喜欢... ...的事情。
I will never make you do anything that you won't... ...like.
如果你敢碰我，我就抓你的脸。
If you try to touch me, I'll scratch your face.
不管谁来，都会看到并问为什么。
And whoever's coming will see and ask why.
这张脸吗?
This face?
现在把电话挂了。
Hang up the phone now.
有一次它响的时候我在这里。
I was down here once when it rang.
哦。最恐怖的事情。
Ooh. Creepiest damn thing.
我认为这是静电造成的。
I think it's static electricity that does it.
我就在旁边的时候它爆炸了。
It went off while I was right next to it.
我想都没想就把它拿了起来。
I picked it up without thinking.
看看有没有人在那
To see if anyone was there.
有吗?
Was there?
不。
No.
救命!
Help!
拜托!
Please!
帮帮我!
Help me!
某人,请!
Somebody, please!
请帮助!
Please help!
停止。停止。阻止它。
Stop. Stop. Stop it.
如果有人能打破那扇窗户，他们早就动手了。
If anyone could've broke that window, they already would've done it.
罗宾会做的。
Robin would've done it.
你别想从这里出去。
You're not getting out of here.
我不出去了。
I'm not getting out of here.
喂?
Hello?
阻止它。
Stop it.
停止什么?
Stop what?
我饿了。
I'm hungry.
我需要食物。
I need food.
你的眼睛怎么样?
How are your eyes?
他们受到伤害。
They hurt.
我不能给你带吃的了。
Well, I can't bring you anything to eat.
你得等等。
You'll have to wait.
楼上有人能看你给我送吃的吗?
Is there someone upstairs who will see you bring me food?
你不用担心这个。
Don't you worry about that.
如果你不打算喂我，为什么还要来这里?
If you weren't gonna feed me, why'd you even come down here?
只是为了看看你。
Just to look at you.
我只是想看看你。
I just wanted to look at you.
我去。
I'll go.
喂?
Hello?
有人在吗?
Is somebody there?
我需要帮助。
I need help.
喂?
Hello?
芬尼。
Finney.
别挂断。
Don't hang up.
我不会的。
I won't.
这是谁?
Who is this?
我不记得我的名字了。
I don't remember my name.
为什么不呢?
Why not?
这是你失去的第一件东西。
It's the first thing you lose.
你什么时候失去的第一件东西?
First thing you lose when?
你知道什么时候。
You know when.
你怎么知道我的名字?
How do you know my name?
我们见面一次。
We met once.
你的手臂是薄荷糖。
Your arm is mint.
你差点就骗到我了。
You almost had me.
布鲁斯?
Bruce?
布鲁斯山田?
Bruce Yamada?
Y-Yeah。
Y-Yeah.
布鲁斯。
Bruce.
哦,我是布鲁斯。
Uh, I'm Bruce.
你的手臂是薄荷糖。
Your arm is mint.
你差点就骗到我了。
You almost had me.
电话响了吗?
Did the phone ring for you?
它响了，但我们都没听见。
It rang, but none of us heard it.
只有你。
Just you.
抓人的人也听到了电话铃声，但他不愿相信。
The Grabber hears the phone, too, but he doesn't want to believe it.
你为什么打电话给我?
Why are you calling me?
你的手臂是薄荷糖。
Your arm is mint.
你差点就骗到我了。
You almost had me.
我很高兴是你。
I'm glad it's you.
芬尼吗?
Finney?
是吗?
Yeah?
走廊的地板上有一段泥土，瓷砖松了。
There's a dirt section of the floor in the hallway where the tile is loose.
好吧。
Okay.
在地基下面挖。
Dig down underneath the foundation.
我试过了，但没有时间从另一边挖出来。
I tried, but there wasn't time for me to dig up and out the other side.
我的时间够吗?
Will I have enough time?
喂?
Hello?
布鲁斯?
Bruce?
我向国旗宣誓效忠。
I pledge allegiance to the flag...
救命!
Help!
我给你做了早餐。
I made you some breakfast.
你在里面放了什么?
What did you put in that?
盐和胡椒。
Salt and pepper.
哦，吃，不吃。
Oh, eat it, don't eat it.
你已经下来了。
You're already down here.
我要给你下药做什么?
What do I need to drug you for?
喂?
Hello?
不要上楼。
Don't go upstairs.
为什么不呢?
Why not?
这是一个陷阱。
It's a trap.
你是…你是布鲁斯吗?
Are you... Are you Bruce?
布鲁斯是谁?
Who's Bruce?
我刚和布鲁斯谈过。
Uh, I was just talking to Bruce.
我不认识什么布鲁斯。
I don't know any Bruce.
他是棒球运动员。
He's the baseball player.
我们这里不打棒球。
We don't play baseball here.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我不记得了。
I don't remember.
你踢足球了吗?足球吗?
Did you play soccer? Football?
我把报纸。
I delivered newspapers.
比利。
Billy.
你是比利肖沃特。
You're Billy Showalter.
也许吧。
Maybe.
不,你是比利。
No, you're Billy.
不…上楼。
Do not... go upstairs.
他在做什么?
What is he doing?
他的等待……在另一边，拿着该死的皮带。
He's waiting... on the other side with that fucking belt.
他没说你可以走，所以如果你想走，他会惩罚你的。
He didn't say you can leave, so if you try, he'll punish you.
他会用皮带打你，直到你昏过去。
He'll beat you with that belt until you pass out.
这很伤我的心,孩子。
It hurts, kid.
疼得很厉害。
It hurts real bad.
你会哭的。
You'll cry.
你会求他停下来的。
You'll beg him to stop.
我们都做到了。
We all did.
但他一直在打败你。
But he just keeps beating you.
喂?
Hello?
哦，可怜的宝贝。
Oh, you poor dear.
去护士办公室打个盹。
Go to the nurse's office and get a nap.
你说我叫比利。
You said my name was Billy.
比利肖沃特。
Billy Showalter.
别那样叫我。
Don't call me that.
我不记得了。这不是我现在的样子。
I don't remember it. It's not who I am now.
那你想让我叫你什么?
What do you want me to call you, then?
你还记得什么?
What do you remember?
我告诉你。
I told you.
我是个报童。
I was a paperboy.
好吧。报童。
Okay. Paperboy.
看到你面前的墙了吗?
See the wall in front of you?
看到墙和地板是怎么分开的了吗?
See how the wall is separated from the floor?
是的。
Yeah.
我从下面扯掉了一根长缆绳。
I tore a long cable loose from down there.
我把它藏起来了。
I kept it hidden.
那我该怎么办?
What am I supposed to do with that?
爸爸?
Daddy?
是的,亲爱的。
Yes, honey.
我可以问你一个问题吗?
Can I ask you a question?
当然。来坐。
Of course. Come sit.
来了。
Come.
那就这样吧。
There you go.
但你保证你不会生气吗?
But you promise you won't get mad?
亲爱的,我保证。
I promise, honey.
是关于我的梦想。
It's about my dreams.
你的梦想呢?
What about your dreams?
如果他们…你知道的,他们……嗯…格温。
Well, what if they... you know, they're... well... Gwen.
你母亲，她是个特别的人。
Your mother, she was a special soul.
她很聪明，和你一样。
And she was smart, just like you.
但是，亲爱的，她也…感动了。
But, sweetheart, she was also, uh... touched.
她看到了什么，听到了什么，她非常确信她的梦有意义。
She saw things and she heard things, and sh-she just became so convinced that her dreams meant something.
最终，他们让她做一些事情。
And eventually, they told her to do things.
可怕的事情。
Terrible things.
所以她结束了自己的生命。
And so she took her own life.
但那不是真的，亲爱的。
But they weren't real, sweetheart.
他们只是不真实。
They just weren't real.
我爱妈妈。
I loved Mom.
我…我也爱她。
I... I loved her, too.
我是说，我爱她原来的样子。
I mean, I loved her the way she was.
我知道,亲爱的。
I know, sweetheart.
我…我…我只是…我不…我不想让你有那样的未来，亲爱的。
I... I... I just... I don't... I don't want that future for you, sweetheart.
你明白吗?
Do you understand?
但是…如果它能帮我找到芬尼呢?
But... wh-what if it could help me find Finney?
嘿!参孙,停止!
Hey! Samson, stop!
来这里!来吧,男孩。来吧。
Come here! Come on, boy. Come on.
等一下。
Hold on one second.
在这里。走了。
Get in here. Go.
-你好吗?-晚上好,先生。
-Hello? -Good evening, sir.
我们在你家附近排查，询问居民，我们想知道，你见过这个男孩吗?
We're canvassing your neighborhood, talking to residents, and we were wondering, have you seen this boy?
你是警察。
You're the police.
-是的。丹佛PD。-嗯。
-Yes. Denver PD. -Uh-huh.
-你是来找失踪的孩子的-是的,先生。
-You're here for the missing kids. -Yes, sir.
如果有什么…不,不。进去。
And if there's anything at all... No, no. Come inside.
来吧。参孙,阻止它!
Come on. Samson, stop it!
正确的。我想给你看样东西。
Right. I want to show you something.
是的，就在这里。
Yeah, right over here.
所有的孩子都住在同一个区，对吧?
So, all the kids live in the same district, right?
他们都步行上学放学。
They all walk to and from school.
他们都是在放学回家的路上被抓的，除了罗宾·阿雷利亚诺——他是在一个周六的下午去商店买汽水和糖果的路上被抓的，对吗?-先生，我们很清楚。
They were all grabbed on the way home from school except for Robin Arellano-- he was grabbed on a Saturday afternoon on his way to the store to get some pop and a candy bar, right? -Sir, we're well aware of that.
只是听。他必须能迅速抓住这些孩子并把他们带回他的住处，也就是说他的房子有车库。
Just listen. He has to be able to grab these kids and get them back to his place very quickly, which means he's got a house with a garage.
他不能冒险让他们跑掉或者在他把他们打晕的时候醒来。
And he can't risk them getting away or waking up if he's knocking them out.
也就是说"抓人者"肯定住在这附近。
Which means that The Grabber has to live somewhere in this area right here.
-,呃…- Max。
-Mr., uh... -It's Max.
-马克斯……-不，不是麦克斯先生。
-Mr. Max... -No, not Mr. Max.
它只是…它只是马克斯。
It's just... it's just Max.
我的朋友叫我麦克斯。既然我们都在一起办这个案子，我想…你在这住了多久了，麦克斯?我…
My friends call me Max. And since we're all working on this case together, you know, I figured... -How long have you lived in the area, Max? -I-I...
不，我住在杜兰戈。我只是在这里借宿。
No, I live down in Durango. I'm just crashing here.
这是我哥哥的家。
This is my brother's place.
我看了很多关于这个案子的报道，我现在正在找工作，你们真的需要我的帮助。
I've been reading about this case a lot, and I'm in between jobs right now, and you guys could really use my help on this.
你继续查，但如果你看到任何一个男孩，给我们打电话。
You keep working at this, but if you see any of these boys, give us a call.
等待。或者如果我有什么新线索，对吧?
Wait. Uh, or if I have any new leads, right?
如果你看到这些男孩，打电话给我。
If you see any of these boys, then call.
你最好在你哥哥回家前收拾一下。
And, uh, might want to tidy up before your brother gets home.
哦。
Oh.
愚蠢，愚蠢，愚蠢的白痴。
Stupid, stupid, stupid moron.
该死的家伙,马克斯。
Goddamn it, Max.
我知道你睡不着。
I know you're not sleeping.
我饿死了。
I'm starving.
-告诉我你的名字。-你为什么这么关心?
-Tell me your name. -Why do you care?
我通常不喜欢。
I usually don't.
我最终在报纸上发现了。
I find out eventually in the paper.
他们总是打印一张漂亮的大照片，上面有我想要的所有细节。
They always print a nice, big photo with all the details I could ever want.
你们撒谎的那些事。
All the things you boys lie about.
这次有什么不同?
What's different this time?
哦……哦,这很复杂。
Oh... Oh, it's complicated.
这是……太复杂了。
It's... too complicated.
一切都是不同的。什么是正确的。
Everything's different. Nothing's going right.
你可以放我走。
You could let me go.
我正在考虑。
I'm thinking about it.
我保证不会告诉任何人。
I promise I won't tell anyone.
你可以蒙上我的眼睛，让我在街上下车。
You can blindfold me, drop me off on the street.
我走路回家。
I'll walk home.
好吧，告诉我你的名字。
Well, tell me your name.
泰勒。
Taylor.
泰勒马伦。
Taylor Mullen.
我真的开始喜欢你了，芬尼。
I was really starting to like you, Finney.
我差点让你走。
I almost let you go.
喂?
Hello?
布鲁斯?
Bruce?
比利,他开始?
Billy--Paperboy?
喂?
Hello?
你没有多少时间了。
You don't have much time.
“掠夺者”一直没睡。
The Grabber hasn't been sleeping.
他认为可能就是这个。
He thinks this might be it.
他会发现的。
That he's gonna figure it out.
谁会知道呢?
Who's gonna figure it out?
他的弟弟在楼上。
His brother upstairs.
你是格里芬吗?
Are you Griffin?
谁?
Who?
格里芬史塔哥。收尾。
-Griffin Stagg. -Probably.
这有点模糊，但我猜你知道我们所有人的名字。
It's all a little hazy, but I imagine you know all our names.
每一个孩子。
Every kid does.
我不认识你。
I didn't know you.
没有人做。
Nobody did.
你隐身这么多年，然后全国的孩子都知道你的名字。
You spend so many years invisible, and then every kid in the state knows your name.
你没有多少时间了。
You don't have much time.
他为什么不杀我?
Why hasn't he killed me?
你不会玩这个游戏。
You won't play the game.
你必须玩游戏。
You have to play the game.
如果你不玩，他就赢不了。
If you don't play, he can't win.
什么游戏?
What game?
淘气的孩子。
Naughty Boy.
如果你不玩Naughty Boy, The Grabber就不能打败你。
If you don't play Naughty Boy, The Grabber can't beat you.
如果他不能打败你，他就无法进入下一阶段。
And if he can't beat you, he can't move on to the next part.
顽皮男孩的下一部分是他最喜欢的部分。
And the next part of Naughty Boy is his favorite part.
下一部分是什么?
What's the next part?
你没有多少时间了。
You don't have much time.
你说。
You said that.
他一直没睡。
He's not been sleeping.
你也这么说过。
You said that, too.
是啊，他现在是了。
Yeah, well, he is now.
在他的椅子上。
In his chair.
他等你玩的时候昏过去了。
He passed out waiting for you to play.
那对我有什么好处?
What good does that do me?
等待。门还没锁。
Wait. The door is still unlocked.
门还没锁。
The door is still unlocked.
我就这么走了吗?
Do I just go?
防风门里面有个密码锁。
There's a combination lock on the inside of the storm door.
-是我的自行车锁。你的自行车锁吗?
-It was my bike lock. -Your bike lock?
是的。他带走我的时候也带走了。
Yeah. He took it when he took me.
组合是什么?
What's the combination?
我不记得了。格里芬。
-I don't remember. -Griffin.
我记得我害怕自己会忘记。
I remember being afraid I'd forget it.
这就是我写下来的原因。
That's why I wrote it down.
什么?在哪里?
What? Where?
我在墙上刻了个瓶盖。
I carved it with a bottle cap in the wall.
墙?这墙? !
Which wall? Which wall?!
右边的那个，当你坐下的时候，和你的肩膀差不多高。
The one on the right, about shoulder height when you're sitting down.
二，三，三，一，七。二，三，三，一，七。
Two, three, three, one, seven. Two, three, three, one, seven.
二，三，三，一，七。
Two, three, three, one, seven.
二，三，三，一，七?
Two, three, three, one, seven?
如果你这么说的话。
If you say so.
但是是23-31-7还是23-3-17还是2-33-17?
But is it 23-31-7 or 23-3-17 or 2-33-17?
我不记得了。格里芬。
-I can't remember. -Griffin.
我不记得了。
I can't remember.
你必须都试一试。
You'll have to try them all.
而且你必须保持沉默。
And you'll have to be very quiet about it.
是的。
Yeah.
好吧。谢谢。
Okay. Thanks.
二，三，三，一，七。二，三，三，一，七。
Two, three, three, one, seven. Two, three, three, one, seven.
救命!
Help!
救命!掠夺者!
Help! The Grabber!
只要你他妈说一个字... ...我会像宰猪一样宰了你
You say one fucking word... ... and I will gut you like a pig right here in the street.
然后用你自己的肠子勒死你。
And strangle you with your own intestines.
晚安，顽皮的孩子。
Nighty night, naughty boy.
我刚才听到的是什么声音?
Hey, what was all that noise I heard?
参孙对着什么东西叫。
Samson was barking at something.
没什么。回床上去，麦克斯。
It's nothing. Go back to bed, Max.
天啊，搞什么鬼?
Jesus, what the fuck?
我是说，搞什么鬼?
I mean, what the fuck?
我向你求助，你却给我这些毫无意义的线索。
I ask you for help, and you give me these clues that don't mean anything.
而今天早上，我醒来却没有任何梦想?
And now this morning, I wake up without any dream at all?
说真的，你到底是怎么了?
Seriously, what the hell is wrong with you?
你让掠夺者带走了芬尼，对吧?
You let The Grabber take Finney, right?
别告诉我你没有参与，因为你一直在给我做这些梦。
And don't tell me that you don't get involved, because you've been giving me these dreams.
除非…
Unless...
也许你根本就不是真的。
Maybe you're not even real.
婊子养的。
Son of a bitch.
不。
No.
去你妈的。
Fuck you.
该死的。
Goddamn it.
什么?
What?
你要说什么吗?
You gonna say something?
你知道你是谁吗?
Do you even know who you are?
这是什么鬼问题?
What the shit kind of question is that?
你知道你是谁吗?
Do you even know who you are?
我是布莱克芬尼。
I'm Finney Blake.
很高兴认识你，芬尼·布雷克。
Yeah, well, nice to fucking meet you, Finney Blake.
在这里。
Right here.
这是它。这是什么?
-This is it. -This is what?
让你可怜的小生命在可怕的噩梦中结束。
The horrifying nightmare end of your pathetic little life.
天呐
Holy shit.
你是万斯斗。
You're Vance Hopper.
我记得你。
I remember you.
你以前常常吓到我。
You used to scare me.
相信我，芬尼·布雷克，如果你知道会发生什么，你会吓坏的。
Trust me, Finney Blake, if you knew what you had coming, you'd be fucking terrified.
就是今天，混蛋。
Today's the day, motherfucker.
♪我不想知道你的名字♪
♪ I don't wanna know your name ♪
♪因为你看起来不一样了♪
♪ 'Cause you don't look the same ♪
♬你以前的方式…♪
♪ The way you did before... ♪
万斯，你会打破你的最高分的。
Vance, you're gonna beat your high score.
我当然会这么做，傻逼。
Of course I'm gonna do it, dumb shit.
我说我会的。
I said I would.
嘿。
Hey.
哦,愚蠢的人!
Oh, jackass!
♪狐狸在奔跑♪
♪ Fox on the run ♪
♬然后躲起来……♪
♪ And hide away... ♪
草泥马!
Motherfucker!
你破坏了我的游戏!
You fucked with my game!
哦，看在上帝的份上。
Oh, for Pete's sake.
-嘿。过来,婊子。
-Hey. -Come here, bitch.
别再耍我了!
Don't fuck with me again!
你知道你是谁吗?
Do you even know who you are?
这是什么鬼问题?
What the shit kind of question is that?
你知道你是谁吗?
Do you even know who you are?
我是布莱克芬尼。
I'm Finney Blake.
很高兴认识你，芬尼·布雷克。
Yeah, well, nice to fucking meet you, Finney Blake.
在这里。这是它。
Right here. This is it.
这是什么?
This is what?
让你可怜的小生命在可怕的噩梦中结束。
The horrifying nightmare end of your pathetic little life.
天呐
Holy shit.
你是万斯斗。
You're Vance Hopper.
我记得你。你以前常常吓到我。
I remember you. You used to scare me.
相信我，芬尼·布雷克，如果你知道会发生什么，你会吓坏的。
Trust me, Finney Blake, if you knew what you had coming, you'd be fucking terrified.
就是今天，混蛋。
Today's the day, motherfucker.
Gwenny,快点。
Gwenny, hurry up.
你上学要迟到了。
You're gonna be late for school.
对不起,爸爸。
Sorry, Daddy.
天呐你是万斯斗。
Holy shit. You're Vance Hopper.
我记得你。你以前常常吓到我。
I remember you. You used to scare me.
相信我，芬尼·布雷克，如果你知道会发生什么，你会吓坏的。
Trust me, Finney Blake, if you knew what you had coming, you'd be fucking terrified.
就是今天，混蛋。
Today's the day, motherfucker.
你试过把地毯堆到窗户那里吗?
Have you tried stacking the carpets to reach the window?
我试着一切。
I've tried everything.
不,不是一切。
No, not everything.
当“抓人者”看到我所做的一切，一切就结束了。
When The Grabber saw what I had done, that was it.
他也花了不少时间陪我。
And he took his time with me, too.
你做了什么?
What did you do?
那个混蛋花了一大笔钱来修理所有的损坏。你做了什么?
Oh, that fucker had to spend a fortune -to repair all the damages. -What did you do?
我马上就说，混蛋!
I'm getting to that, cunt wad!
还是你现在有其他重要的事要做?
Or do you have some other important shit you have to do right now?
不，不，不，我…我在听。
No, no, no, no, I'm... I'm listening.
厕所里有个插座，就在厕所对面。
There's an outlet in the shitter, across from the john.
是的，我看过。
Yeah, I've seen it.
在墙的另一边，有个储藏室。
On the other side of that wall, there's a storage room.
你进不去那个房间，因为有个超大的直立式冰柜挡着你。
You can't get into that room, because there's a big-ass upright freezer in the way.
好吧。
Okay.
在插座上方约两英尺的墙上敲一下，直到你找到一个有螺丝的面板。
Break into the wall about two feet above the outlet till you get to a panel with screws in it.
把面板拿开，你就进了冷冻室。
Get the panel off, you're into the freezer.
然后去了储藏室。
And then out into the storage room.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
为了什么?
For what?
对我的帮助。
For helping me.
帮你?
Helping you?
这与你无关。
This isn't about you.
他妈的他…!
Fuck him...!
什么?
What?
嘿,芬恩。
Hey, Finn.
发生什么事情了?
What's happening?
罗宾?
Robin?
嘿,哥们。别哭了。
Hey, buddy. Don't cry.
我不是。
I'm not.
是的,你是。
Yes, you are.
我能看见你。
I can see you.
你可以吗?我和你在一起。
-You can? -I'm with you.
我一直都和你在一起。
I've been with you this whole time.
你有吗?
You have?
一个人绝不会丢下朋友不管。
A man never leaves a friend behind.
我爸爸去越南时没有丢下他的朋友。
My dad didn't leave his buddies behind when he went to 'Nam.
这就是他没回家的原因。
That's why he didn't come home.
我也不回家了。
And I'm not coming home, either.
我不会丢下你不管的。
And I'm not going to leave you behind.
我们很快就会再在一起。
We'll be together again soon.
他妈的。你不会像我那样去的。
Fuck that. You ain't gonna go like I did.
我试着一切。任何的工作。
I've tried everything. Nothing's worked.
特效。罗宾…你还记得我跟你说的吗?
-Yet. -Robin... Do you remember what I told you?
说我要看《德州电锯杀人狂》
That I needed to see Texas Chain Saw Massacre?
在这之前。
Before that.
总有一天我要为自己挺身而出。
That someday I have to stand up for myself.
“某一天”就是今天，芬恩。
"Someday" is today, Finn.
今天是你不再受任何人欺负的日子。
Today's the day you stop taking shit from anybody.
我不像你那样是个斗士，罗宾。
I'm not a fighter like you, Robin.
你连他都带不走。
You couldn't even take him.
你一直都是个斗士，芬恩。
You've always been a fighter, Finn.
这就是我们的共同点，我们成为朋友的原因。
That's what we have in common, why we were friends.
你总是害怕出拳，但你总是知道如何承受。
You were always afraid to throw a punch, but you always knew how to take one.
每次你都能站起来。
And you always got back up every time.
我不够强壮。
I'm not strong enough.
你必须这样做。你要离开这里。
You have to be. You're getting out of here.
如果你不能为自己做，那就为我做。
If you can't do it for you, do it for me.
这有什么关系?
What does it matter?
因为我不想白白送死。
Because I don't want to die for nothing.
我希望至少为一个朋友而死。
I want to at least have died for a friend.
因为我杀不了那个贱人，你得帮我。
And because I can't kill that hijo de puta, you have to do it for me.
如何?
How?
你要用武器。
You're gonna use a weapon.
什么武器?
What weapon?
你手里的那个。
The one in your hand.
电话?
The phone?
把接收器装满泥土。
Fill the receiver with dirt.
包紧点
Pack it in tight.
用点力
Give it some heft.
然后呢?
Then what?
然后你一遍又一遍地练习。
Then you practice over and over.
你拿起电话。快速后退一步。
You raise the phone. Take a fast step back.
向前一步，后退一步，然后挥棒。
Step forward, step back and swing.
试试它吧。-现在?
-Try it. -Now?
是的。
Yes.
你拿起电话。快速后退一步。
You raise the phone. Take a fast step back.
向前一步，后退一步，然后挥棒。
Step forward, step back and swing.
再来。你拿起电话。快速后退一步。
Again. You raise the phone. Take a fast step back.
向前一步，后退一步，然后挥棒。
Step forward, step back and swing.
再来。你拿起电话。快速后退一步。
Again. You raise the phone. Take a fast step back.
向前一步，后退一步，然后挥棒。
Step forward, step back and swing.
再来。你拿起电话。快速后退一步。
Again. You raise the phone. Take a fast step back.
向前一步，后退一步，然后挥棒。
Step forward, step back and swing.
你明白了。
You got it.
现在按我说的往手机里灌土。
Now fill the phone with dirt like I told you.
我还能跟你说话吗?
Will I still be able to talk with you?
这是最后一通电话，芬恩。
This was the last call, Finn.
从现在开始都是你的了。
It's all you from here on out.
我想你，罗宾。
I miss you, Robin.
那就为我出去。
Then get out for me.
用我们给你的东西。
Use what we gave you.
我会的。
I will.
再见,芬恩。
Bye, Finn.
再见,罗宾。
Bye, Robin.
请,亲爱的耶稣。请,请。
Please, dear Jesus. Please, please.
对不起，我说你不是真的。
I'm sorry I said you weren't real.
请真实的。请。
Please be real. Please.
请,请,请。
Please, please, please.
请侦探赖特。
Detective Wright, please.
没有该死的方法。
No fucking way.
我知道他在这里对我有所隐瞒，但圣母玛利亚。
I knew that he was hiding something from me down here, but holy Mary, mother of God.
请帮助。
Please, help.
你能给我爸打个电话吗?叫我姐姐?
C-Can you call my dad? Call my sister?
哦,听。别担心，他不在这里。
Oh, listen. Don't worry, he's not here.
他得去工作了。
He-he had to go into work.
我是麦克斯，伙计。Stay-stay平静。
Uh, I'm Max, man. Stay-stay calm.
难怪他今天早上会抓狂。
No wonder he was freaking out this morning.
你想知道我是怎么找到你的吗?
Hey, you want to know the story about how I found you, man?
-不，不，不…-嘿，不，不，不。
-No, no, no, no... -Hey, no, no, no.
别担心。我们可以谈谈……
Don't worry about it. We can talk about this...
是这所房子吗?
Is this the house?
-是的。——你确定吗?
-Yes. -Are you sure?
今天之前我从没见过，除了在梦里。
I'd never seen it before today, except in my dreams.
树，门，地址，大门。
The tree, the door, the address, the gate.
每一个细节。
Every detail.
好吧。好了，退后。
Okay. Okay, you-you s-step back.
与她同住。
Stay with her.
请快点。
Please hurry.
好的,我们走吧。
Okay, let's go.
看看你让我做了什么。
Look what you made me do.
你逼我杀了我弟弟。
You made me kill my brother.
不。
No.
这不是我。我…他是个白痴。
It wasn't me. I... He was an idiot.
但他是我的白痴。
But he was my idiot.
对不起,马克斯。
I'm sorry, Max.
现在我要把你和其他人放在一起。
Now I'm gonna have to put you with the others.
看来你还是会找到那些淘气的孩子的。
Looks like you'll find those naughty boys after all.
打开!警察!
Open up! Police!
电话怎么了?
What's up with the phone, huh?
我告诉过你没用的!
I told you it doesn't work!
通常我会用刀。
Normally, I would use a knife.
但你很特别，芬尼。
But you are special, Finney.
我要慢慢来。
I'm gonna take my time.
我希望这真的很痛。
I want this to really hurt.
参孙!
Samson!
明确。明确!
-Clear. -Clear!
好男孩。
Good boy.
它是空的。-走错房子了。
-It's empty. -It's the wrong house.
这是为你。
It's for you.
欢迎来到你悲惨人生的噩梦尽头。
Welcome to the nightmare end of your pathetic little life.
你没有多少时间了。
You don't have much time.
就是今天，混蛋。
Today's the day, motherfucker.
我杀不了你，你这个小贱人，所以芬恩会帮我的。
I can't kill you, you hijo de puta, so Finn is gonna do it for me.
芬恩的胳膊是薄荷糖!
Finn's arm is mint!
等待。
Wait.
我们有一个地下室。
We've got a basement.
是那些失踪的孩子。
It's the missing kids.
这是他埋葬他们的地方。
This is where he buries them.
我觉得他是在别的地方杀的。
I think he kills them someplace else.
我认为你是对的。
I think you're right.
嘿,嘿,嘿。嘿。跟我来。
Hey, hey, hey. Hey. Come with me.
地下室。地下室。
-Basement. -Basement.
带孩子们离开这里。
Get the kids out of here.
背后的障碍。
Behind the barrier.
我很抱歉。
I am so sorry.
我——我……我很……我很抱歉。
I'm-I'm... I'm so... I'm so sorry.
请原谅我。
Please forgive me.
我是丹佛警察局的沃克局长。
My name is Chief Walker of the Denver Police Department.
我们社区漫长的噩梦终于在今晚以苦乐参半的结局结束了，失踪的布莱克孩子终于获救了，同时我们还发现了五具尸体，我们相信这是该地区其他失踪儿童的尸体。
Our community's long nightmare has finally come to a bittersweet end tonight with the rescue of the missing Blake child but also the discovery of five bodies we believe to be the other missing children in the area.
以下是破案的人提供的案件事实。
Here are the facts of the case by the men who broke it.
侦探赖特?-谢谢,长官。
-Detective Wright? -Thanks, Chief.
这名行凶者被称为“抓人者”，他拥有两处住所，其中一处是他在受害者活着的时候把他们关在那里，另一处是街对面的空屋，他把他们埋在那里。
The perpetrator known as The Grabber owned two homes, one where he kept the victims while alive and a second empty home across the street where he buried them postmortem.
是他吗?就是他。
-Is that him? -That's him.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
-你看到他了吗?-我以为他会更大。
-Did you see him? -I thought he would be bigger.
就是他杀了掠夺者。
He's the one who killed The Grabber.
这就是他。-不。
-That's him. -No way.
Grabber大概有7英尺高。
The Grabber was like seven feet tall.
我听说他捅了他。
I heard he stabbed him.
那孩子怎么能把他勒死?
How could that kid strangle him to death?
-是一把斧头砍在头上。-我爸爸是警察。我知道。
-It was an axe to the head. -My dad's a cop. I know.
我听说他用手机把他打死了。
I heard he beat him to death with a phone.
早上好。
Good morning.
嗨,芬尼。
Hi, Finney.
叫我芬恩。
Call me Finn.
♪你的脸上有微笑♪
♪ There's a smile on your face ♪
♬这里离你家很远
♪ It's a long way from your home ♪
♪远离你所熟知的所有伤痛
♪ Far from all the pain that you have ever known ♪
♬走了，没有痕迹
♪ Gone without a trace ♪
♬这只鸟已经从火里飞走了
♪ Up from the fire this bird has flown ♪
当你在优雅中展开翅膀
♪ As you spread your wings in grace ♪
♬你并不孤单
♪ You're not alone ♪
♪还有你的恐惧♪
♪ And your fear ♪
♬它走了
♪ It is gone ♪
♪把一切都留在家里♪
♪ Left it all inside that home ♪
♬你永远不会孤单
♪ You will never be alone ♪
♪一直都是♪
♪ As I have been ♪
♪所有你曾经拥有的感情♪
♪ All of the feelings you have had ♪
♪还有一种感觉如此糟糕的伤害
♪ And a hurt that felt so bad ♪
♪♪让你坚强，不会让你疯狂
♪ Make you strong, won't make you mad ♪
♬它消失了♬
♪ It disappears ♪
♬你的脸上有一个微笑
♪ And there's a smile on your face ♪
♬这里离你家很远
♪ It's a long way from your home ♪
♪远离你所熟知的所有伤痛
♪ Far from all the pain that you have ever known ♪
♬走了，没有痕迹
♪ Gone without a trace ♪
♬这只鸟已经从火里飞走了
♪ Up from the fire this bird has flown ♪
♪当你在空间里展翅♪
♪ As you spread your wings in space ♪
♬你并不孤单
♪ You're not alone ♪
♪你远离家乡♪
♪ You're far from home ♪
♬走了，没有痕迹
♪ Gone without a trace ♪
♬这只鸟已经从火里飞走了
♪ Up from the fire this bird has flown ♪
♪当你在空间里展翅♪
♪ As you spread your wings in space ♪
♬你并不孤单
♪ You're not alone ♪
♪你远离家乡♪
♪ You're far from home ♪
♬是的，你的脸上有微笑
♪ Yes, there's a smile on your face ♪
♬这里离你家很远
♪ It's a long way from your home ♪
♪远离你所熟知的所有伤痛
♪ Far from all the pain that you have ever known ♪
♬走了，没有痕迹
♪ Gone without a trace ♪
♬这只鸟已经从火里飞走了
♪ Up from the fire this bird has flown ♪
当你在优雅中展开翅膀
♪ As you spread your wings in grace ♪
♬你并不孤单
♪ You're not alone ♪
♪你远离家乡♪
♪ You're far from home ♪
♬你离这里很远，是啊♬
♪ You're really far from here, yeah ♪
♬你并不孤单
♪ You're not alone ♪
♬现在没有什么可害怕的了
♪ There's nothing left to fear now ♪
♬你真的离家很远了
♪ You're really far from home ♪
♬你离这里很远，是啊♬
♪ You're really far from here, yeah ♪
♬你永远不会孤单
♪ You'll never be alone ♪
♬你永远不会孤单。♪
♪ You'll never be alone. ♪
♬今天是周末♬
♪ It's the weekend ♪
我想起了好朋友
♪ I think of good friends ♪
♪有时候会忘记自己死了♪
♪ Sometimes forget they died ♪
♬我想看他们
♪ I want to see them ♪
♪因为我需要♪
♪ Because I need them ♪
♬它会让你哭
♪ It can make you cry ♪
♬它继续走
♪ And it goes on ♪
♪ It goes on ♪
♬它继续走